<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[vocalfreq]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[vocalfreq]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/vocalfreq/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2016 19:32:19 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/vocalfreq/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[john Grove part2]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>john Grove part2</h1><p>This is "john Grove part2" by on Vimeo, the home for high quality videos and the people who love them.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/a9a23b759bc1f23e9eff94b3ea73d474b3ae967e.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://vimeo.com/126493768</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">e7a99bff-1436-44f7-b326-f2ce7dbb2103</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2016 19:32:18 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>The Potential of Math as Medicine by Sharry Edwards, MEd  Studies conducted by the non-profit Institute of BioAcoustic Biology, located in Albany, Ohio,  USA, has shown that persons with similar stresses, toxins, diseases, traumas, genetic  syndromes, deficiencies…have similar, if not identical, vocal anomalies showing that math can  be much more than a measurement tool. Math, as a frequency matrix, can serve as the  template to perceive and manage health and wellness.  In order to provide predictability and safety, the concepts of math and medicine often act  conjointly to quantify, define and model medical practice. Defined as Bioinformatics1  , this  industry has become an integral part of medical care.  The Journal of BioAcoustic Biology (http://www.JBAB.org) reports the studies conducted by the  non-profit Institute of BioAcoustic Biology, located in Albany, Ohio, USA, which have  consistently demonstrated that math can be much more than a measurement tool; math, as  frequency, can be the resolution to therapeutic predictability, management and resolution.  Consider the brain as the central processing unit of the body. Brain messages (as frequency  impulses) use a neural network distributed throughout the body to organize, interpret and  maintain equilibrium (homeostasis). Everything that is perceived by the body reaches the brain  (from various sensory organs) as a biofrequency that is then sorted, routed and assigned an  interpretation and designation.  Studies by the Institute of BioAcoustic Biology affirm the fact that persons who hold similar  perceptions and psychologies; and those suffering from similar diseases, traumas, toxins,  deficiencies, syndromes… have similar, if not identical, biofrequency patterns.  The Business of Disease: An Inside Job and Outside Business edited by Sonia Barrett2  includes  a chapter devoted to explaining the pathways of compounds called Chemistry; as they relate to  Mathways of subtractive frequencies that can be used to create a numeric biomarker matrix  capable, individually and collectively, of being predictive, diagnostic and prescriptive. The  Making History by   Creating the Future chapter speculates that resonate matrix-based medicine has the ability to provide prompt and  corrective protocols.  To date there is no universally accepted modality that has the potential to assist in the survival  of biological, radioactive and pandemic threats; reverse stroke and muscle trauma or support  space travel as frequency based solutions show the ability to overcome bone-loss and muscle  atrophy. The Washington Post (Sept 12, 2014)3  reports that in many instances, by the time the  cause has been identified, it is often too late to provide remediation.  A previous project in conjunction with the US Army4 was undertaken to test this emerging  technology by exploring the potential of using frequency based biomarkers to identify and  quantify Traumatic Brain Injury (TBI) and associated Post Traumatic Stress Disorder (PTSD).  The implication of the prior  study was the development of  a quantitative, mobile, noninvasive  model that could  identify the damage caused  by close proximity acoustic  blast injuries and, ultimately,  the restitution of normal brain  function and emotional  stability. The work being  pioneered by the Institute  continues to employ numeric biomarker patterns to assess, evaluate and produce outcomes  that support optimal biological form and function.  Brian Butterworth, author of What Counts: How Every Brain is Hardwired for Math5  states that  our brain communicates using the language of math expressed as frequency. As these signals  reach the brain, the biofrequencies are sorted, routed and assigned an interpretation and  responsibility. Our brain and our biology are hardwired to respond to these basic principles of  math.  This novel math-based protocol utilizes the premise that the body can identify and prescribe for  itself using the algorithms of vocalized frequencies to accurately quantify, organize, and  extrapolate biometric information. Experimental studies showing the reversal of hip/joint pain;  the reversal of Macular Degeneration and a study of Pitocin induced labor can be found  at: http://www.SoundHealthOptions.com - ARTICLES.  Jill I. Matteson, author of Sound Secrets: Ultimate Healing6  believes that BioAcoustic Biology is  an area of scientific endeavor that is in the process of becoming scientifically established. She  reports that visionary leaders see this model as a prophecy for a new medicine which can  provide conclusions based on measurable outcomes and observation. This emerging paradigm  will become part of future medicine as the consistent and efficacious outcomes continue to  accrue. This protocol remains in a research mode as of the date of this writing.  Strange, yet profound, BioAcoustic Biology may someday explain how a physician might instruct  a heart patient to “listen to a specific frequency combination [known for its ability to stabilize  heart rhythm] and call me in the morning”.  References:  “This novel protocol utilizes the premise that the body  can identify and prescribe for itself using algorithms of  vocalized frequencies to accurately quantify, organize,  and extrapolate biometric information.” 1BioInformatics: Oxford Journals. Current issue: Volume 30, Issue 18, September 15  2014.http://bioinformatics.oxfordjournals.org  2Barrett, Sonia. Business of Disease: An Inside Job and Outside Business. 2013. Sovereign  Mind Publications: Chapter 5.  3America’s infuriating response to the Ebola crisis. The Washington Post. (Attiah) September  12, 2014  4Innovative Ohio Biotech Company Awarded Contract with US Army to Study Traumatic Brain  Injury and Post Traumatic Stress Disorder 2009. Health Plus Letter Vol. 6, No 19.  http://www.1healthyworld.com/eZine/vol6no19.html  5Butterworth, Brian. What Counts: How Every Brain is Hardwired for Math, 1999. Free Press  6Jill I. Matteson. Secret Sounds: Ultimate Healing, 2011. An authorized biography concerning  the cutting-edge work of pioneer Sharry Edwards and energy medicine.</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/vocalfreq/the-potential-of-math-as-medicine-by-sharry-edwards-med-st/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">ab3c95c5-e9c8-4a3d-9318-3af6c61f160f</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2016 19:28:36 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Computerized biometric frequency
modeling used to detect and compile mathematically designed disease, staging
and diagnostic biomarkers]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Computerized biometric frequency
modeling used to detect and compile mathematically designed disease, staging
and diagnostic biomarkers</h1><p></p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/eb62973f5b72255e275b6e8dd6133ce0a676e3dc.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/vocalfreq/f1b3fc19-85cf-46fa-8efe-fd79f4900327/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">f1b3fc19-85cf-46fa-8efe-fd79f4900327</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2016 09:15:32 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Human BioAcoustics® Our bridge between the ancient ideas of sound healing and the futuristic Star Trek. ]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Human BioAcoustics® Our bridge between the ancient ideas of sound healing and the futuristic Star Trek. </h1><p>Everything that happens to the body reaches the brain as biofrequencies that are then
sorted, routed and assigned an interpretation but it seems, in modern times, that we
carry very little conscious awareness of this information. Did we as a human race forget,
or were we politically forced to abandon, a great deal of our intrinsic abilities that allow
us to glean information about another person simply by hearing their voice? </p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/b9ec13c1e3d396bcbc9ebb306b9ea33421435acb.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/vocalfreq/human-bioacousticsr-our-bridge-between-the-ancient-ideas-of/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">d79ced6f-1773-4317-8593-ad605788c86a</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2016 15:43:23 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>